You don't have to protect me. I'm not afraid.
Je hoeft me niet te beschermen. Ik ben niet bang.
Please don't shut me out again.
Sluit me niet opnieuw buiten
Don't shut me out again
Please don't slam the door
Sla de deur niet dicht
Don't slam the door
You don't have to keep your distance anymore
En verstop je toch niet meer, kom in het licht!
And don't hide any more, come in the light!
'Cause for the first time in forever
Want voor het eerst in heel mijn leven
'Cause for the first time in my life
I finally understand
Kan ik het nu verstaan
I can understand it now
For the first time in forever
Voor het eerst in heel ons leven
For the first time in our lives
We can fix this hand in hand
Kunnen wij dit samen aan
We can do this together
We can head down this mountain together.
Deze berg afdalen met z'n tweeën
Head down the mountain as the two of us
You don't have to live in fear
En geen angst meer, maar plezier
And no more fear, but fun
'Cause for the first time in forever
Want voor het eerst in heel mijn leven
'Cause for the first time in my life
I will be right here
Blijf ik bij je hier
I will stay here with you
Anna.
Anna!
Please go back home
Ga toch naar huis
Go back home
Your life awaits
Het leven wacht
Go enjoy the sun, and open up the gates
Geniet van de zon die door het venster lacht
Enjoy the sun that smiles through the window
Yeah, but...
Ja, maar...
I know.
Ik weet 't
I know
You mean well, but leave me be
Het is okee, maar ach laat mij
It's okay, but leave me
Yes, I'm alone
Ik ben alleen
I'm alone
But I'm alone and free
Maar ben alleen en vrij
Just stay away and you'll be safe from me
Blijf bij me weg, ver weg, veilig voor mij
Stay away from me, far away, safe from me
Actually, we're not
Maar dat ben ik niet
But I'm not
What do you mean, you're not?
Wat bedoel je niet
I get the feeling you don't know
Ik weet niet hoe ik het zeggen zou
I don't know how I should say it
What do I not know?
Hoe je zeggen zou
How you should say it!?
Arendelle's in deep, deep, deep
Arendelle is in diepe, diepe, diepe
deep snow
diepe kou
deep cold
What?
Wat?
You kind of set off an eternal winter everywhere.
Je veroorzaakte een eeuwige winter, en overal!
You caused an eternal winter, and everywhere!
Everywhere?
Overal?
Well, it's okay, you can just unfreeze it.
Maar da's oke, je kan het toch ontvriezen
But that's okay, you can unfreeze it anyway
No, I can't. I don't know how.
Nee dat kan ik niet, ik weet niet hoe
No I can't, I don't know how
Sure you can. I know you can.
Tuurlijk wel. Ik weet dat je het kan.
Of course. I know you can do it.
'Cause for the first time in forever
Want voor het eerst in heel jou leven
'Cause for the first time in your life
Oh, I'm such a fool! I can't be free!
Ooh, ik ben zo stom! Ik ben niet vrij!
Ohh, I'm so stupid! I'm not free!
You don't have to be afraid
Hoef je niet meer bang te zijn
You don't have to be afraid any more
No escape from the storm inside of me
Geen ontsnappen aan de storm die lijd in mij
No escape from the storm that howls in me
We can work this out together
Ja het lukt ons wel tezamen
Yes it will work out together
I can't control the curse!
Ben nooit vrij van de vloek
I'm never free of that curse
We'll reverse the storm you've made
En die storm krijgen we klein
And we will defeat that storm
Anna, please you'll only make it worse!
Maak het niet erger met je bezoek
Don't make it worse with your visit
Don't panic!
Geen angst meer
No fear any more
There's so much fear!
De angst zit hier
The fear is here
We'll make the sun shine bright
Nadat de zon weet schijnt
After the sun shines again
You're not safe here!
Ga weg van hier
Go away from here
We can face this thing together
En die oude vloek versplinterd
And that old curse will splinter
No!
Nee!
We can change this winter weather
We verdrijven deze winter
We will face this winter
And everything will be all right
Totdat deze zon weer gaat schijnen
Until the sun is shining again
I can't!
Gaat niet!