It's Coronation Day!
Het is kronings dag!
It's coronation day!
The window is open!
De ramen gaan open
The windows are opening
So's that door!
en kijk die deur
and look at that door
I didn't know they did that any more
De hele hal heeft nu al veel meer kleur
The whole hallway already has a lot more color
Who knew we owned 8,000 salad plates?
Wel duizend borden met een gouden boord
A thousand plates with a gold board
For years I've roamed these empty halls
Al jaren leef ik zonder doel
For years I live without purpose
Why have a ballroom with no balls?
In het paleis zonder gevoel
In the palace without feeling
Finally, they're opening up the gates!
Eindelijk ze openen de poort
Finally they do open the gate
There'll be actual, real, live people
Al die blije echte mensen
All those real happy people
It'll be totally strange
Ik zie ze allemaal staan
I see them all stand
But wow! Am I so ready for this change!
En ik kan die verandering wel aan
And I do have that change
'Cause for the first time in forever
Want voor het eerst in heel mijn leven
Because for the first time in my life
There'll be music, there'll be light
Klinkt muzeik en is er licht
Sound of music and there is light
For the first time in forever
Voor het eerst in heel mijn leven
For the first time in my life
I'll be dancing through the night
Dans ik met een blij gezicht
I dance with a happy face
Don't know if I'm elated or gassy
Ben ik uitgelaten of in extase
I am elated and ecstatic
But I'm somewhere in that zone
Dit is ech een fenomeen
This is a phenomenon
'Cause for the first time in forever
Want voor het eerst in heel mijn leven
Because for the first time in my life
I won't be alone
Ben ik niet alleen
I'm not alone
I can't wait to meet everyone!
Ik kan niet wachten om iedereen te ontmoeten
I can't wait to meet everyone
What if I meet The One?
Misschien ontmoet ik "Die Ene"?
Maybe I will even meet "The One"?
Tonight, imagine me gown and all
Vanavond met baljurk in de zaal
Tonight with ball gown in the room
Fetchingly draped against the wall
Mooi gedrapeerd tegen een paal
Beautifully draped against a pole
The picture of sophisticated grace
Een toonbeeld van een koninklijke stijl
An example of a royal style
I suddenly see him standing there
En plotseling zie ik hem daar staan
And suddenly I see him standing there
A beautiful stranger, tall and fair
Die man met z'n mooiste kleren aan
That man with his best clothes
I wanna stuff some chocolate in my face!
Wat chocolade vlug in al mijn keel
Want chocolate quickly in my throat
But then we laugh and talk all evening
Maar heel de avond blijft hij bij mij
But all the evening he stays with me
Which is totally bizarre
En dat is toch heel erg raar
And that is very strange
Nothing like the life I've led so far
Vroeger ging het anders eerlijk waar
It used to be different, honestly
For the first time in forever
Voor het eerst in heel mijn leven
For the first time in my life
There'll be magic, there'll be fun
Zal ik naar een dansfeest gaan
Should I be going to a dance party
For the first time in forever
Voor het eerst in heel mijn leven
For the first time in my life
I could be noticed by someone
Misschien ziet iemand mij nu staan
Maybe now someone sees me stand
And I know it is totally crazy
En ik weet 'k zal de liefde niet vinden
And I know I will not find love
To dream I'd find romance
Al bij mijn eerste dans
With my very first dance
But for the first time in forever
Maar voor het eerst in heel mijn leven
But for the first time in my life
At least I've got a chance!
Krijg ik nu toch een kans
I now get a chance, at least!
Don't let them in
Laat niemand toe
Let no one in
Don't let them see
Kijk niemand aan
Don't look at anyone
Be the good girl you always have to be
Je moet altijd het brave meisje zijn
You always have to be the good girl
Conceal, don't feel
Geen blik, geen snik
No look, no sob
Put on a show
Het masker op
Put on the mask
Make one wrong move and everyone will know
Één foutje en de boel staat op z'n kop
One mistake and everything is upside down
But it's only for today
't Is alleen maar voor vandaag
It's only for today
Alleen maar voor vandaag
Only for today
It's agony to wait
Die pijn hier in mijn maag
That pain here in my stomach
It's agony to wait
Die pijn hier in mijn maag
That pain here in my stomach
Tell the guards to open up
Wachters ga en open nu
Guardians go now and open
The gate
De poort
For the first time in forever
Voor het eerst in heel mijn leven
For the first time in my life
Don't let them in, don't let them see
Laat niemand toe, kijk niemand aan
Let no one in, don't look at anyone
I'm getting what I'm dreaming of
Durf ik geloven in mijn droom
I dare to believe in my dream
Be the good girl you always have to be
Je moet altijd het brave meisje zijn
You always have to be the good girl
A chance to change my lonely world
Een kans voor een heel nieuw verhaal
An opportunity for a whole new story
Conceal
Geen blik
No look
A chance to find true love
Vol liefde zonder schroom
Full of love without shame
Conceal, don't feel, don't let them know
Geen blik, geen snik, het masker op
No look, no sob, put on the mask
I know it all ends tomorrow
En morgen zal het voorbij zijn
And tomorrow it will be over
So it has to be today!
dus vandaag is echt mijn dag!
so today is my day!
'Cause for the first time in forever
Want voor het eerst in heel mijn leven
Because for the first time in my life
For the first time in forever
Voor het eerst in heel mijn leven
For the first time in my life
Nothing's in my way!
Voel ik dat het mag
I feel that it should