Okay, can I just say something crazy?
Oké, mag ik eens, iets heel geks zeggen?
Okay, can I, say something really crazy?
I love crazy.
Ik hou van gek.
All my life has been a series of doors in my face
Al mijn hele leven gaat steeds de deur voor mij dicht
All my life the door closed in front of me
And then suddenly I bump into you
En nu plotseling bots ik tegen u
And now suddenly I crash into you
I was thinking the same thing, because, like...
Ik was net hetzelfde aan het denken, want weet je...
I was just thinking the same, because you know...
I've been searching my whole life to find my own place
Ik zoek heel mijn leven all waar mijn plekje ligt
I'm searching my whole life for where my place is
And maybe it's the party talking, or the chocolate fondue
En misschien is het wel dit feestje of de choco fondue
And maybe it's this party, or the chocolate fondue
But with you
Maar met jou
But with you I found my place
Maar met jou zie ik 't licht
But with you I see the light
I see your face
Zie jou gezicht
And it's nothing like I've ever known before
En als zoiets je een keertje overkomt
And if something like that happens to you some time
Love is an open door!
Is liefde een open deur!
Love is an open door
Is liefde een open door
With you
Met jou
Love is an open door
Is liefde een open deur
I mean, it's crazy
Het is wel grappig
It's funny
What?
Wat?
We finish each other's
We delen elkaars ge(dachten)
We finish each other's (thoughts)
Sandwiches
(Ge)bakken vis
Baked fish!
That's what I was gonna say!
Dat ging ik net zeggen!
I was going to say that!
I've never met someone
Je denkt precies als ik
You're thinking exactly like me
Who thinks so much like me
Ja dat is echt een feit
Yes, that's a real fact
Jinx! Jinx again!
Wens! Nog eens wens!
Wish! Wish again!
Our mental synchronization
Die samen denken ervaring
That together-thinking experience
Can have but one explanation
Heeft maar één enkele verklaring
Does have one simple explanation
You and I were just meant to be
Jij en ik samen voor altijd
You and me together forever
Say goodbye
Zeg vaarwel
To the pain of the past
Het verdriet is voorbij
The pain is over
We don't have to feel it anymore
Als wij alle dingen zien in kleur
If we see all things in color
Love is an open door
Is liefde een open deur
Love is an open door!
Is liefde een open deur!
Life can be so much more
't leven is zoveel meer
Life is so much more
With you
Met jou
Love is an open
Is liefde een open
Door
Deur
Can I say something crazy?
Mag ik eens iets geks zeggen?
Will you marry me?
Wil je met me trouwen?
Can I say something even crazier?
Mag ik nog iets veel gekkers zeggen?
Yes!
Ja!