Reindeers are better than people
Dieren zijn beter dan mensen
Animals are better than people
Sven, don't you think that's true?
Sven, 't is waar geef toe
Sven, it's true, admit it
"Yeah, people will beat you and curse you and cheat you"
"Ja, mensen bedriegen, ze slaan je en liegen"
"Yes, humans deceive, they slap you and lie"
"Every one of them's bad, except you!"
"Maar jij bent wel een held, man, en hoe!"
"But you are a real hero, man, and how!"
Aw. Thanks, buddy.
Bedankt, maatje.
Thanks, buddy.
But people smell better than reindeers
Ze ruiken wel beter dan dieren
They do smell better than animals
Sven, don't you think I'm right?
Sven, had je dat gedacht?
Sven, did you think about that?
"That's once again true, for all except you!"
"Dat is ook weer waar, behalve jij daar"
"That's also true, except for you"
You got me! Let's call it a night.
Betrapt! Maar nu goeienacht.
Got me! But now goodnight.
"Good night"
"Slaap zacht"
"Sleep tight"
Don't let the frostbite bite.
Hou de kou uit je hart
Keep the cold away from your heart