(English) Elsa?
(Flemish) Elsa?
(Transl.) Elsa?
Do you wanna build a snowman?
Kom dan maken we een sneeuwman
Come then we build a snowman
Come on, let's go and play
Ik speel niet graag alleen
I don't want to play alone
I never see you any more
Je moet toch eens naar buiten ooit
You have to look outside once!
Come out the door
Ik zie je nooit
I never see you
It's like you've gone away
't Is net of je verdween!
It's like you disappeared!
We used to be best buddies, and now we're not
We waren beste vriendjes, en nu niet meer
We were best friends, and now no longer
I wish you would tell me why
Dus zeg me waar het aan lag
So tell me what it was
Do you wanna build a snowman?
Kom dan maken we een sneeuwman?
Come then, we build a snowman?
It doesn't have to be a snowman
Kan ook iets anders dan een sneeuwman
Can also be something other than a snowman
Go away, Anna.
Ga weg, Anna
Go away, Anna
Okay, bye
Oke, dag
The gloves will help.
De handschoenen helpen.
See? Conceal it.
Zie je? Geen blik...
Understand? No look...
Don't feel it.
Geen snik.
No sob.
Don't let it show.
Het masker op.
Put on the mask.
Do you wanna build a snowman?
Kom dan maken we een sneeuwman?
Come then, we build a snowman?
Or ride our bike around the halls?
Of we gaan fietsen in de hal
Or go cycling in the hall
I think some company is overdue
Want voor gezelschap is de hoogste tijd
It's high time for companionship
I've started talking to the pictures on the walls
Ik praat al tegen de portretten in de zaal
I'm talking to the portraits on the walls
Hang in there, Joan.
Volhouden Jeanne
Hold on, Joan
It gets a little lonely, all these empty rooms
Ik voel me wel wat eenzaam in dit leeg paleis
I do feel a little lonely in this empty palace
Just watching the hours tick by
De klok tikt de uren weg
The clock is ticking away the hours
I'm scared.
Ik ben bang
I'm scared
It's getting stronger!
Het wordt sterker!
Getting upset only makes it worse. Calm down.
Als jij je opwindt wordt het alleen maar erger. Rustig maar.
If you are excited you will only make it worse. Calm down.
No! Don't touch me!
Nee, raak mijn neit aan!
No, don't touch me!
Please, I don't want to hurt you.
Alsjeblieft, ik wil u geen pijn doen
Please, I (don't) want you to hurt
See you in two weeks!
Tot over twee weken!
Do you have to go?
Moeten jullie echt weg?
Do you really have to go?
You'll be fine, Elsa.
Het komt goed, Elsa.
It will be fine, Elsa.
Your Highness.
Uwe majesteit
Your majesty.
Elsa?
Please, I know you're in there
Alsjeblieft, 'k weet dat je daar bent
Please, I know you're there
People are asking where you've been
De mensen zeggen: "Kind hou moed"
The people say: "Child, keep your spirits up"
They say "Have courage", and I'm trying to
En ik blijf hopen, want ik hou van jou
And I keep hoping, because I love you
I'm right out here for you
En ik ben hier voor jou
And I'm here for you
Just let me in
Laat mij erin
Let me in
We only have each other; it's just you and me
We zijn maar met z'n tweeën, alleen jij en ek
The two of us are still together, just you and me
What are we gonna do?
Wat moeten wij nu doen?
What should we do now?
Do you wanna build a snowman?
Kom dan maken we een sneeuwman?
Come then, we build a snowman?