Summer?
Zomer?
Oh. I don't know why,
Ik weet niet waarom,
I don't know why,
but I've always loved the idea of summer
maar ik heb altijd van gedroomd van de heerlijk zomer
but I've always dreamed of that beautiful summer
and sun, and all things hot.
en de zon en lekker warm...
and the sun, and nicely warm...
Really?
Echt waar?
I'm guessing you don't have much experience with heat.
Ik wet dat je niet veel evaring hebt met hitte
I bet you don't have much experience with heat
Nope.
Nee!
No!
But sometimes I like to close my eyes,
Maar soms sluit ik gewoon mijn ogen
But sometimes I just close my eyes
and imagine what it would be like when summer does come.
en beeld ik me in hoe het zou zijn in de zomer.
And I imagine how it would be in the summer.
Bees will buzz, kids will blow dandelion fuzz
Bij zoemt blij, paardenbloem pluisje in de wei
Bee buzzes happily, dandelion fluff in the meadow
And I'll be doing whatever snow does in summer
En ik doe alles wat sneeuw doet in de zomer
And I do everything snow does in summer
A drink in my hand
Een glas in mijn hand
A glass in my hand
My snow up against the burning sand
Mijn sneeuw warmt zich(?) in het warme zand
My snow warming itself(?) in the warm sand
Probably getting gorgeously tanned
Ik word lekker zonnebruin
I'm gonna be sun-browned
In summer.
In de zomer
In the summer
I'll finally see a summer breeze
Een winter storm drijven ver
A winter storm is drifting far
Blow away a winter storm
op een zachte zomer bries
on a soft summer wind
And find out what happens to solid water
En kijk wat er gebeurd met bevroren water
And look what happens with frozen water
When it gets warm
als het niet vriest
if it's not freezing
And I can't wait to see
En wat zalen mijn vrienden
And what shall my friends
What my buddies all think of me
zeggen als ze me zien?
say when they see me?
Just imagine how much cooler I'll be
Want ik zal zoveel cooler zijn in
Because I will be cooler
In summer!
de zomer!
in the summer!
The hot and the cold are both so intense
De warmte en koud zijn zo intens
The warmth and cold are intense
Put them together It just makes sense
Zet ze bij één, is alles naar wens
Put them together, everything is fine
Winter's a good time to stay in and cuddle
Zit elke dag op een zonnig terrasje
Every day I'm sitting at a sunny terrace
But put me in summer and I'll be a...
En o, in de zomer word ik een...
And oh, in summer, I'll be a...
(puddle?)
(plasje?)
(little puddle?)
Happy snowman!
blije sneeuwman!
happy snowman!
When life gets rough
Zit het niet mee
It isn't easy
I like to hold on to my dream
Dan vlucht in weg in fantasie
So I walk away in fantasy
Of relaxing in the summer sun, just letting off steam
Van relaxen in de zomer zon wat een magie
From relaxing in the summer sun, that's magic
Oh, the sky will be blue
O, die lucht is zo blauw
Oh, the sky is so blue
And you guys will be there, too
Ben bij jullie van wie ik hou
I am with you whom I love
When I finally do
Als ik eindelijk doe
When I can finally do
What frozen things do in summer!
wat een sneeuwman doet in de zomer!
what a snowman does in summer!
I'm gonna tell him.
Ik ga het hem zeggen.
I'm going to tell him.
Don't you dare.
Durf het niet!
Don't you dare!
In summer!
De zomer!
The summer!